ROBERT MICHAEL

THOMPSON

10 Dukes close London, CM16 6DA 01992524644 07951081088 Rthom69@gmail.com



http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0860648/ - to access a selection of my credits. full credit list available on request.

SUMMARY

I have 20 years experience working in Audio post production in and around London. I have worked on many genres of projects from Film to tv drama, docudrama, documentary, promos and commercials.

I work as a dubbing mixer, sound editor/designer, vo recordist, ADR recordist and foley recordist.

I am the recipient of a Cinema Audio Society award for outstanding achievements in audio mixing as part of the audio Post Production team for the Channel 4 mini series "Shakelton"

My most recent position is Manager and Audio supervisor for SKY Vision, a production company and international distribution company, owned by SKY broadcasting. I run their Audio post production facility in London's west end.

I have excellent working knowledge of Protools, Fairlight Dream2 and Logic Audio software. I have a strong working knowledge of post production workflows and systems.

I have worked as a staff member, freelancer and manager, where I have been responsible for maintaining the facility and making sure it is current to fulfil the company needs, as well as scheduling and overseeing junior staff and hiring freelancers when necessary.

I contributed to the current SKY vision technical audio delivery specification, distributed to production companies for all their international acquisitions.

References available on request.

SKILLS

- Strong Technical background and knowledge of Audio Production
- 20 years experience in Audio post production in London's West End.
- Creative and self motivated.
- Excellent working knowledge of Protools, Fairlight Dream2 and Logic Audio.
- Mixing sound designing/editing for many genres

- Project management
- Team liaison
- Strong verbal communication
- Extremely organised
- Team leadership
- Process implementation
- Client assessment and analysis

WORK HISTORY

Audio Supervisor/Facility Manager

SKY Vision Sound — 6 Grafton Mews Fitzrovia London

Day to Day running of an Audio post production Facility in London's West End. Maintaining the 2 x 5.1 Audio suites, training junior staff, Making upgrades, keeping

software current, Scheduling work, assisting Directors and Producers to meet their technical and Artistic requirements, Supervising Audio deliverables for the International Distribution arm (Sky vision), Sound Mixing/design and Editing Long form and short form content, hiring Freelancers.

05/2007 - 05/2012**Head of Sound**

Parthenon Entertainment — ChorleyWood London

Senior Dubbing mixer/sound designer working on a variety of long form and short form projects including Docudramas, wildlife and Factual shows. day to day running of studios, scheduling and ensuring client producers and Directors technical and

artistic requirements were satisfied.

09/2005 - 05/2007Freelance Dubbing mixer/Editor

Freelance

Working freelance in and around London on a variety of projects including TV Drama,

Film, Factual and Foley and ADR recording.

Dubbing mixer 01/2003 - 09/2005

Saint Annes Post — Warder street London

Dubbing mixer/ sound editor working on TV Drama, TV Film and ADR and VO

recording.

Dubbing Mixer 06/1997 - 09/2002

> dB Post — Berwick street London Dubbing Mixer/ Sound editor.

EDUCATION

1996 HND (Distinction): Music/Audio technology

London College Of Music — Thames Valley University